https://movetolearn.com/cookie-policy-eu/

This cookie statement was last updated on 2nd June 2020 and applies to citizens of the European Economic Area.1. IntroductionOur website, https://movetolearn.com (hereinafter: “the website”) uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as “cookies”). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of programme code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. Cookies5.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.5.2 Analytical cookiesWe use analytical cookies to optimise the website experience for our users. With these analytical cookies we get insights in the usage of our website. We ask your permission to place analytical cookies.5.3 Marketing/Tracking cookiesMarketing/Tracking cookies are cookies or any other form of local storage, used to create user profiles to display advertising or to track the user on this website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.5.4 Social media buttonsOn our website we have included buttons for Facebook, LinkedIn, WhatsApp and Instagram to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook, LinkedIn, WhatsApp and Instagram. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook, LinkedIn, WhatsApp and Instagram themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymised as much as possible. Facebook, LinkedIn, WhatsApp and Instagram are located in the United States.6. Placed cookiesGoogle Analytics
Usage
We use Google Analytics for website statistics. Read more
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Statement.
Statistics (anonymous)
Name
_ga
Retention
2 years
Function
Name
_gid
Retention
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
Google Fonts API
Retention
none
Function
Request user IP address
Google reCAPTCHA
Usage
We use Google reCAPTCHA for spam prevention. Read more
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google reCAPTCHA Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
rc::c
Retention
session
Function
Filter requests from bots
Name
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Maps Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
Google Maps API
Retention
none
Function
Request user IP address
Vimeo
Usage
We use Vimeo for video display. Read more
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Vimeo Privacy Statement.
Statistics
Name
__utmt_player
Retention
10 minutes
Function
Store and track audience reach
Name
Sharing data
For more information, please read the SoundCloud Privacy Statement.
Functional
Name
sc_anonymous_id
Retention
10 years
Function
Provide functions across pages
Name
Usage
We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
actppresence
Retention
1 year
Function
Manage ad display frequency
Name
Usage
We use LinkedIn for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
Sharing data
For more information, please read the LinkedIn Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
bcookie
Retention
2 years
Function
Store browser details
Name
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Complianz Privacy Statement.
Functional
Name
complianz_policy_id
Retention
365 days
Function
Store accepted cookie policy ID
Name
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Automattic Privacy Statement.
Statistics
Name
tk_ai
Retention
session
Function
Store a unique user ID
WooCommerce
Usage
We use WooCommerce for webshop management. Read more
Sharing data
This data is not shared with third parties.
Functional
Name
wc_cart_hash_*
Retention
session
Function
Store items in shopping cart
Name
Sharing data
For more information, please read the JetPack Privacy Statement.
Statistics
Name
tk_tc
Retention
session
Function
Store the user’s usage history
Name
Sharing data
For more information, please read the MailChimp Privacy Statement.
Statistics
Name
mailchimp_landing_site
Retention
1 month
Function
Store which page was visited first
Marketing/Tracking
Sharing data
For more information, please read the YouTube Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
GPS
Retention
session
Function
Store location data
Functional
Function
7. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on “Save preferences”, you consent to us using the categories of cookies and plug-ins you selected in the pop-up, as described in this Cookie Policy. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.7.1 Manage your consent settings8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Data Protection Authority).9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.Please note that our website may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Malcolm Manning, MoveToLearn
Neustiftgasse 54/30
1070 Wien
Austria
Website: https://movetolearn.com
Email: malcolm_manning@movetolearn.com
Phone number: +436704048617This Cookie Policy was synchronised with cookiedatabase.org on 18th June 2020Share this:TwitterFacebook
Why learn to move when you can move to learn?
Join the mailing list
Impressum www.movetolearn.com is the website of:
© 2020 movetolearn.
How to sit at a desk, work at a computer … and maybe even enjoy it!
Caring For Our Necks
Falling in love with falling … or learning to love the floor
Feldenkrais Method individual lessons for children with special needs
Workshops
Words
